easycalculation.com 2015-03-24

# Privacy policy

#### PRIVACY POLICY

Thank you for visiting EasyCalculation.com. Your privacy is very important to us. Simply stated, our policy is to collect no personal information about you when you visit the EastCalculation.com Web site, unless you affirmatively choose to make such information available to us.

When you visit the EasyCalculation.com web site, the Web server automatically recognizes only the Internet domain and IP address from which you accessed the site. This information does not result in the identification of your personal e-mail address or other personal information.

In addition, information is only gathered regarding the volume and timing of access to the site by collecting information on the date, time and pages you visited while at the site. This is done so that the content of the site can be improved, and your personal information is not identified.

If any visitor to the site chooses to provide us with personal information, as in an email inquiry, that information will be used only to respond to the message. The information will not be used for any purpose other than to respond to the inquiry. We do not create individual profiles from the information provided or distribute the information to other organizations.

We do not collect information or profile of our visitors in any way. This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we, easycalculation.com, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information.

**Advertisements**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies.

**Cookies**

Advertisements may display on this web site and, if so, may set and access cookies on your computer; such cookies are subject to the privacy policy of the parties providing the advertisement. These parties usually use non-personally-identifiable or anonymous codes to obtain information about your visits to this site.If you want to find out more information about this practice, and to learn about your options, including your options with regard to the following companies that may serve advertising on this site.
